

SKILLS

- Working with developer tools (WebStorm, VS Code, Sublime Text, Warp)
- Graphic design (Figma, Canva, Photoshop, Illustrator)
- Working with videographer's tools (Premiere Pro, After Effects, Final Cut)
- PC assembly and configuration
- Blind printing

LET'S TALK:

+992 (55) 999-55-45 Tajikistan, Dushanbe T.Pulodi str., 37, 734001

mahmadali_h@icloud.com <u>maxhalimov.github.io/about-me</u> Telegram: @max_halimov

RECOMMENDATIONS:

Rajabali Halimov Director, NGO "Dilsuzi" +992 (918) 68-23-93 r_halimov@mail.ru

Mahmadali Halimov

ABOUT ME:

I started getting interested in IT technologies from childhood, when I was about 12 years old. Back then, my path to IT started from scratch, and I progressed in small steps, becoming better. I intend to continue to rise in this industry.

EXPERIENCES

Volunteer as an IT specialist

NGO "Dilsuzi"

JANUARY 2020 - PRESENT

- Website maintenance dilsuzi.tj
- Create designs for posters on social networks.
- Typography.

Volunteer as a Cameraman and Video Editor

NGO "Dilsuzi"

JUNE 2020 - present

- Participation in more than 30+ video projects.
- Installation of commercials and promotional videos.
- Professional installation using specialized software.

EDUCATION

Secondary School No. 8 in Dushanbe

- Graduated in 2023.
- Winner of the Presidential Scholarship 2021-2022.

Ilmhona Skills Accelerator School

- Front-end Developer Program Level 1
- Front-end Developer PRO program
- Released in 2024.
- During the program, many modern and promising Front-end development libraries have been studied
- Confident ownership of the Git system.

IT-RUN Academy

- React Developer Program
- Released in 2024.

The Skillbox educational platform

- Profession: Internet marketer
- In the process of studying



ТЕХНИЧЕСКИЕ УМЕНИЯ

- Работа с инструментами разработчика (WebStorm, VS Code, Sublime Text, Warp)
- Графический дизайн (Figma, Canva, Photoshop, Illustrator)
- Работа с инструментами видеографа (Premiere Pro, After Effects, Final Cut)
- Сборка и настройка ПК
- Слепая печать

ДАВАЙТЕ ПОГОВОРИМ:

+992 (55) 999-55-45 Таджикистан, г. Душанбе ул. Т.Пулоди, д. 37, 734001 mahmadali_h@icloud.com maxhalimov.github.io/about-me Telegram: @max_halimov

РЕКОМЕНДАЦИИ:

Раджабали Халимов Директор, ОО «Дилсўзй» +992 (918) 68-23-93 r_halimov@mail.ru

Махмадали Халимов

моя история:

Я начал увлекаться IT-технологиями с детства, когда мне было примерно 12 лет. Тогда мой путь в IT начинался с нуля, и я маленькими шажками прогрессировал, становился лучше. Я намерен продолжать подниматься в этой отрасли.

ОПЫТ РАБОТЫ

Волонтер в качестве ІТ-специалиста

ОО "Дилсӯзй" ЯНВАРЬ 2020 Г. - НАСТОЯЩЕЕ ВРЕМЯ

- Ведение сайта dilsuzi.tj
- Создание дизайнов для постеров в соцсетях.
- Типографика.

Волонтер в качестве Оператора и Видеомонтажера

ОО "Дилсӯзй" июнь 2020 г. - настоящее время

- Участие в более 30+ видео-проектов.
- Монтаж роликов и рекламных видеоматериалов.
- Профессиональный монтаж с использованием специализированного программного обеспечения.

ОБРАЗОВАНИЕ

Средняя Общеобразовательная Школа №8 г.Душанбе

- Выпущен в 2023г.
- Обладатель Президентской стипендии 2021 2022г.

Школа «ilmhona» акселератор навыков

- Программа Front-end разработчик Уровень 1
- Программа Front-end разработчик PRO
- Выпущен в 2024 г.
- В ходе программы изучены много современных и преспективных библиотек Front-end разработки
- Уверенное владение Git-системой.

Академия IT-RUN

- Программа React-разработчик
- Выпущен в 2024 г.

Образовательная платформа «Skillbox»

- Профессия Интернет-маркетолог
- В процессе изучения